
=== CO1 (89 questions) ===
  [2M] What is DBMS?
  [2M] What is the role of Storage Management?
  [2M] What is a Database?
  [2M] What is a Query processor?
  [2M] What is schema?

=== CO2 (151 questions) ===
  [2M] What is ER Model?
  [2M] What are tuples and attributes in relational database?
  [2M] Give any two benefits of a data model.
  [2M] What is a derived attribute?
  [2M] What is a Foreign Key?

=== CO3 (119 questions) ===
  [2M] Write the syntax of SQL Rename operation.
  [2M] What is a tuple variable and write the syntax of its usage.
  [2M] Can we drop a primary key constraint? If so, what is the syntax of that query?
  [2M] Give the different syntaxes of SELECT query.
  [2M] In which type of Query is the WHERE clause used?

=== CO4 (125 questions) ===
  [2M] What is a nested subquery? Provide an example.
  [2M] What are the different types of joins in SQL?
  [2M] Define a view in SQL and explain its advantages.
  [2M] Write a SQL query to create a view for employees with a salary greater than 50000.
  [2M] Write a SQL query to grant SELECT privilege on a table to a user.

=== CO5 (208 questions) ===
  [2M] What is meant by partial functional dependency?
  [2M] Define Pitfalls in Relational Database Design.
  [2M] Describe the concept of redundancy in relational databases.
  [2M] Explain the impact of inconsistent data on relational database design.
  [2M] What are anomalies in relational databases? Discuss how update, insertion, and deletion anomalies occur.

=== CO6 (221 questions) ===
  [2M] In order to undo the work of transaction after last commit, which step is used?
  [2M] Define the concept of a transaction in a database.
  [2M] What are the advantages of serial execution of transactions over concurrent execution?
  [2M] List the types of locks used in lock-based concurrency control protocols.
  [2M] What is the significance of the ôBeginö and ôCommitö operations in transaction management?
